newmediacampaigns.com 2019-05-02

# New Media Campaigns Privacy Policy - New Media Campaigns

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://www.newmediacampaigns.com (the “Site”).

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.  
\- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.  
\- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and information Submitted voluntarily through the site's web forms.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our visitor browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

**SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

DO NOT TRACK  
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

DATA RETENTION  
When you submit information through the Site, we will maintain your Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

CHANGES  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US  
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@newmediacampaigns.com or by mail using the details provided below:

110 E. Main St. Suite 200, Carrboro, NC, 27510, United States
